{
    "subject": "Norman_Mailer",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Maidstone__film_",
    "human_readable": "Norman Mailer directed the film Maidstone.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8934494853019714,
            "question": "Who directed the film Maidstone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.872238039970398,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Norman Mailer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7924124598503113,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Norman Mailer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.775025486946106,
            "question": "Was Norman Mailer involved in filmmaking?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7310469746589661,
            "question": "Did Norman Mailer act in any films he directed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.613961935043335,
            "question": "What is the title of the film Maidstone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3680974245071411,
            "question": "What genre is the film Maidstone likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3251332938671112,
            "question": "Besides writing, what other artistic pursuit was Norman Mailer known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.062023814767599106,
            "question": "Can you name another film directed by a famous author?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03702552244067192,
            "question": "Why might an author choose to direct a film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norman Mailer directed the film Maidstone.",
            "html": "yago_28874_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another film directed by a famous author?",
            "html": "yago_28874_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides writing, what other artistic pursuit was Norman Mailer known for?",
            "html": "yago_28874_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Maidstone likely to be?",
            "html": "yago_28874_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28874_77.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Norman Mailer wrote, produced, and directed the film Maidstone, among other things. This information supports the triple that Norman Mailer directed the film Maidstone."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Norman Mailer wrote, directed, and starred in the film \"Maidstone,\" which supports the statement that Norman Mailer directed the film Maidstone."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}